A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Grants E-G FA732C FA732C
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Ford Foundation Grants - E to G
  - Education Development Center, Inc. (07000192), 1970 February 01-1971 March 31 (Reel 1541)
    STUDY OF FEAS. OF NATL, NONGOVTL BODY ON EDUC. & LICENSING OF SCHOOL PERSONNEL & DEV. OF PLAN FOR ESTAB. OF SUCH A BODY
    $58,500.00;$58,500.00
    Kelly, James A.
  - Education Development Center, Inc. (07100276), 1971 January 01-1971 December 31 (Reel 1730)
    SUPPORT FOR INNOVATIVE APPROACHES TO CURRICULUM DEVELOPMENT IN BIOLOGY
    Myers, Robert G.
  - Education Development Center, Inc. (07300191), 1972 December 01-1973 November 30 (Reel 2626)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT FOR PLANNING A CENTER FOR RETRAINING SCHOOL PRINCIPALS IN THE EASTERN MASSACHUSETTS AREA
  - Education Development Center, Inc. (07400034), 1973 October 15-1974 October 14 (Reel 1494)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT OF A FILM-BASED HIGH SCHOOL CURRICULUM PROJECT ON THE ROLE OF WOMEN IN AMERICAN SOCIETY
    $60,046.00;$60,046.00
  - Education Development Center, Inc. (07550120), 1974 December 01-1975 September 01 (Reel 1094)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT OF A FILM-BASED CURRICULUM PROJECT ON THE ROLE OF WOMEN IN AMERICAN SOCIETY
  - Education Development Center, Inc. (07600146), 1976 January 01-1980 December 31 (Reel 2268;2269)
    SUPPORT FOR FIELD TRIALS OF PROJECT TORQUE MATHEMATICS TESTS
    $339,819.00;$339,819.00
    Lynch, Barbara D.;Martus, Marjorie
  - Education Development Center, Inc. (07850182), 1977 December 15-1979 April 01 (Reel 2742)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT FOR THE DEVELOPMENT OF AN IN SERVICE TRAINING CAPACITY AT EDC.
    $25,000.00;$21,211.68
  - Education Development Center, Inc. (07850558), 1978 May 01-1979 October 30 (Reel 2810)
    PARTIALLY RECOVERABLE GRANT PROVIDING SUPPORT TO PUBLISH, PROMOTE AND DISTRIBUTE A STUDY OF CHILD CARE SYSTEMS IN THE PUBLIC SCHOOLS
    Berresford, Susan V. (Susan Vail);Brown, Prudence
  - Education Development Center, Inc. (08450035), 1983 October 01-1984 June 30 (Reel 4632;4633)
    SUPPORT TO PRODUCE BOOKLET DESCRIBING AND ANALYZING REPORTS ON RECENT STUDIES OF AMERICAN PUBLIC SCHOOLS
    United States; Education Development Center, Inc.
  - Education Development Center, Inc. (08500888), 1985 September 01-1994 September 30 (Reel 6888;6889)
    TO PROVIDE TECHNICAL ASSISTANCE TO ELEVEN URBAN MATHEMATICS COLLABORATIVES AND TO BEGIN REPLICATION ACTIVITY
    $3,598,552.00;$3,598,552.00
    Nelson, Barbara S.;Hatton, Barbara R.
  - Education Development Center, Inc. (08750751), 1987 July 01-1989 March 31 (Reel 6786)
    TO PLAN AND DESIGN AN INFORMATION CAMPAIGN FOR THE URBAN MATHEMATICS COLLABORATIVES
    $14,300.00;$14,300.00
    Nelson, Barbara S.
  - Education Development Center, Inc. (08851014), 1988 May 01-1989 April 30 (Reel 6226)
    TO PROVIDE STAFF SUPPORT FOR A SERIES OF MEETINGS ON TEACHERS NETWORKS
  - Education Development Center, Inc. (08851131), 1988 September 01-1989 September 30 (Reel 5759)
    SUPPORT TO DEVELOP A GUIDE FOR PLANNING IMPROVEMENTS IN THE EDUCATION OF AT-RISK STUDENTS IN URBAN SCHOOLS
    $39,215.00;$39,215.00
  - Education Development Center, Inc. (09350837), 1993 June 01-1994 February 11 (Reel 6819)
    SUPPORT FOR THE PLANNING AND DEVELOPMENT OF A NATIONAL ADULT LITERACY INITIATIVE BASED ON TELEVISION AND VIDEO.
    Education & Culture Program [EC];Urban Poverty Program [UP]
    Bernstein, Alison R.;Curvin, Robert
  - Education Development Center, Inc. (09400774), 1994 February 01-1998 February 28 (Reel 7555)
    CONTINUED SUPPORT TO IMPLEMENT A NATIONAL ADULT LITERACY MEDIA INITIATIVE
    Urban Poverty Program [UP];Education & Culture Program [EC];US & International Affairs Programs - Office Of Vice President [USIAP/OVP]
    $3,090,000.00;$3,090,000.00
    Bernstein, Alison R.;Curvin, Robert;Mincy, Ronald B.;Zwerling, L. Steven
  - Education Development Center, Inc. (09701513), 1997 September 01-2001 November 30 (Reel 8812)
    CONTINUED SUPPORT FOR PRODUCTION, RESEARCH AND EVALUATION, COMMUNITY OUTREACH, MARKETING, AND CORE OPERATIONS OF THE ADULT LEARNING AND MEDIA ALLIANCE PROJECT
    Education, Sexuality, Religion;Human Development and Reproductive Health;KC & F - Office of the Vice President;Assets - Office of the Vice President;Media Arts and Culture;Economic Development
    $5,300,000.00;$5,300,000.00
    Santos, John Phillip;Colborn, John L.
  - Education Development Center, Inc. (10050451), 1999 December 01-2002 July 31 (Reel 8990)
    SUPPORT FOR THE HOUSTON-NEWARK TELECOLLABORATION PROJECT, WHICH LINKS, FOR PROFESSIONAL DEVELOPMENT PURPOSES, A GROUP OF PROJECT GRAD TEACHERS IN THE TWO CITIES VIA TELECOMMUNICATIONS TECHNOLOGY
    Zwerling, L. Steven
    Houston (Tex.); Newark (N.J.); Teachers--Texas--Houston (Tex.)--Services for; Teachers--New Jersey--Newark (N.J.)--Services for; Telecommunication; Teachers--Training of; Education -- Aims and objectives; Education Development Center, Inc.
  - Education Development Center, Inc. (10051204), 2000 April 01-2001 March 31 (Reel 8524)
    STUDY ON THE EFFECTIVENESS, IMPACT AND VALUE OF YOUTH MEDIA TRAINING PROGRAMS IN THE UNITED STATES
    Funabiki, Jon
    United States; Educational equalization -- United States; Education -- Aims and objectives; Education Development Center, Inc.
  - Education Development Center, Inc. (10200326), 2002 January 01-2005 January 31 (Reel 9162)
    Core support for the Adult Literacy Media Alliance project
    Economic Development;Human Development and Reproductive Health;Media Arts and Culture;Education, Sexuality, Religion;Assets - Office of the Vice President
    $2,000,000.00;$2,000,000.00
    Colborn, John L.;Floyd, Virginia Davis;Wilkerson, Margaret B. (Margaret Buford);Petrovich, Janice;Santos, John Phillip;Campbell, Elizabeth C.
  - Education for Life Foundation, Inc. (09700734), 1997 February 01-1999 August 31 (Reel 8115)
    SUPPORT FOR TRAINING PROGRAMS FOR VILLAGE AND COMMUNITY-BASED LEADERS
    Hawes, Gary A.
    Philippines; Education for Life Foundation, Inc.
  - Education for Life Foundation, Inc. (10251870), 2002 September 01-2003 August 31 (Reel 9180)
    To provide distance education to school dropouts in partnership with local governments
    Philippines (Manila)
    $87,000.00;$87,000.00
    Guevara, Milwida
  - Education for Life Foundation, Inc. (10351180), 2003 July 01-2005 June 30 (Reel 9151)
    To establish an alternative learning system for out-of-school youth and adult learners from indigenous communities in five provinces
  - Education Fund for Southern Africa (09201160), 1992 September 01-1993 September 01 (Reel 6765)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT FOR BLACK SOUTH AFRICAN AND NAMIBIAN STUDENTS COMPLETING BACHELORS AND MASTERS DEGREES IN THE U.S.
    $28,000.00;$28,000.00
    Namibia; South Africa; Education Fund for Southern Africa
  - Education Fund of Family Planning Advocates of New York State (09801374), 1998 June 01-2002 December 31 (Reel 9196)
    SUPPORT FOR MERGERWATCH
    $247,000.00;$247,000.00
    Winters, David
    United States; Women--Health and hygiene--New York (State); Birth control -- New York (State); Education Fund of Family Planning Advocates of New York State
  - Education Fund of the American Center for International Labor Solidarity (10100197), 2000 November 01-2002 October 31 (Reel 9211)
    Support to strengthen the capacities of Southeast Asian trade unions and partner civil society organizations to address international financial issues
    Human Rights;Indonesia (Jakarta);Philippines (Manila)
    $425,000.00;$425,000.00
    Lindblom, Lance E.;Siskel, Suzanne E.;Hawes, Gary A.
    SouthEast Asia; Labor unions--SouthEast Asia; International finance; International economic relations; Education Fund of the American Center for International Labor Solidarity
  - Education Law Center, Inc. (07300659), 1973 October 01-1985 September 30 (Reel 4961;4962)
    GENERAL SUPPORT FOR THE CENTER'S PUBLIC INTEREST LAW AND EDUCATIONREFORM ACTIVITIES
    $2,750,000.00;$2,750,000.00
    United States; Education Law Center, Inc.
  - Education Law Center, Inc. (08600239), 1986 January 01-1987 September 30 (Reel 5769)
    SUPPORT TO DOCUMENT CAUSES AND RATES OF SCHOOL DROPOUTS IN URBAN COMMUNITIES IN NEW JERSEY
    New Jersey; Education Law Center, Inc.
  - Education Law Center, Inc. (09701534), 1997 July 01-1998 June 30 (Reel 7897)
    SUPPORT TO PLAN SYSTEMIC SCHOOL REFORM ACTIVITIES
    Aguerrebere, Joseph;Driver, Cyrus;Petrovich, Janice;Zwerling, L. Steven
  - Education Quality Institute (10200718), 2002 January 01-2002 December 31 (Reel 9111)
    To develop and disseminate summary research reports on widespread education reform models and to develop an organizational sustainability plan
    United States; Education Quality Institute
  - Education Resources Group, Inc. (08951247), 1989 September 01-1993 February 28 (Reel 6272)
    SUPPORT TO DEVELOP A REPORT ABOUT THE FORD FOUNDATION SUPPORTED PROGRAM OF URBAN COMMUNITY-SCHOOL COLLABORATIVES TO PREVENT DROPOUTS
    $86,885.00;$86,885.00
    Meade, Edward J.;Hatton, Barbara R.
    United States; Education Resources Group, Inc.
  - Education Resources Group, Inc. (08951303), 1989 September 01-1993 December 31 (Reel 6904)
    SUPPORT FOR A FOLLOW-UP STUDY OF THE "MIDDLE COLLEGE" HIGH SCHOOL PROGRAM
    Bernstein, Alison R.;Zwerling, L. Steven
  - Education Resources Group, Inc. (09450238), 1993 November 01-1995 April 30 (Reel 6904)
    SUPPORT TO CONDUCT A NEEDS ASSESSMENT AND TO PROVIDE TECHNICAL ASSISTANCE FOR FOUR NEIGHBORHOOD AND FAMILY INITIATIVE SITES
    $72,000.00;$72,000.00
    Bernstein, Alison R.;Petrovich, Janice
    United States; Detroit (Mich.); Hartford (Conn.); Memphis (Tenn.); Education Resources Group, Inc.
  - Education Resources Group, Inc. (10001455), 2000 July 01-2002 June 30 (Reel 8897)
    SUPPORT FOR DOCUMENTATION AND EVALUATION OF NEW VOICES FELLOWSHIP PROGRAM
    United States; Education, Higher -- United States; Policy sciences--Study and teaching--Evaluation; Education Resources Group, Inc.
  - Education Resources Institute (10100842), 2001 March 01-2002 February 28 (Reel 8881)
    Support to establish the National Alliance for College Access and Success
    Driver, Cyrus;Zwerling, L. Steven
    United States; Educational change -- United States; Educational equalization -- United States; Education, Higher -- United States; Education Resources Institute
  - Education Resources Institute (10300660), 2003 March 01-2003 December 31 (Reel 9001)
    For the dissemination and implementation activities of the National Alliance for College Access and Success
    United States; Education Resources Institute
  - Education Task Force (07350526), 1973 May 07-1973 August 06 (Reel 1773)
    SUPPORT OF THE SEMINAR WORKSHOP FOR THE REGIONAL SCIENCE TEACHING CENTERS
    $755.00;$755.00
    Frodin, Reuben
    Philippines; Education Task Force
  - Education Writers Association (07950017), 1978 November 01-1978 December 31 (Reel 2593)
    PREPARATION AND DISTRIBUTION OF BACKGROUND PAPERS ON ISSUES IN EDUCATION
    $2,100.00;$2,100.00
    United States; Education Writers Association
  - Education Writers Association (08050269), 1980 January 15-1980 March 31 (Reel 2265)
    SUPPORT FOR THE SECOND SPECIAL SEMINAR ON MAJOR ISSUES IN EDUCATION
    $3,818.00;$3,818.00
  - Education Writers Association (08750221), 1987 February 01-1987 June 30 (Reel 5642)
    SUPPORT TO STUDY AND EVALUATE A PILOT PROJECT TO ENGAGE TEACHERS IN COMMUNITY SOCIAL SERVICE AGENCIES
    $20,700.00;$20,700.00
    Tennessee; Education Writers Association
  - Education, Training and Research Associates (08300402), 1983 April 01-1985 March 31 (Reel 4915)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT OF NATIONAL NETWORK FOR FAMILY LIFE EDUCATION
    United States; Education, Training and Research Associates
  - Education, Training and Research Associates (08600228), 1986 January 01-1986 December 31 (Reel 5134)
    Harkavy, Oscar
  - Education/instruccion, Inc. (07750073), 1977 January 01-1978 July 01 (Reel 1316)
    SUPPORT FOR A DEMONSTRATION PROGRAM TO PROMOTE OPEN HOUSING
    National Affairs [NA]
    Chandler, Robert W.
    Education/instruccion, Inc.
  - Educational Beginnings Inc. (08550660), 1985 May 23-1986 May 22 (Reel 4983;5547)
    SUPPORT AFRICAN PARTICIPANTS IN THE INTERNATIONAL WOMEN'S STUDIES INSTITUTE IN KENYA
    $8,200.00;$8,200.00
    Africa, East; Africa, Southern; Educational Beginnings Inc.
  - Educational Broadcasting Corporation (06100240), 1961 September 26-1962 September 25 (Reel 0253)
    PURCHASE OF AN EDUCATIONAL TELEVISION STATION IN THE NEW YORK AREA
    Educational Broadcasting Corporation
  - Educational Broadcasting Corporation (06100256), 1961 July 17-1962 July 16 (Reel 0253)
    PROGRAM DEVELOPMENT FOR EDUCATIONAL TELEVISION IN THE NEW YORK AREA
  - Educational Broadcasting Corporation (06200138), 1962 February 07-1966 June 26 (Reel 0253)
    INITIAL OPERATION OF AN EDUCATIONAL TELEVISION STATION IN THE NEW YORK AREA
    $3,494,000.00;$3,494,000.00
  - Educational Broadcasting Corporation (06600024), 1965 November 19-1971 June 09 (Reel 1435)
    GENERAL SUPPORT FOR COMMUNITY EDUCATIONAL TELEVISION STATIONS
    Dressner, Howard R.
  - Educational Broadcasting Corporation (06700267), 1967 May 17-1977 May 16 (Reel 5608)
    MATCHING GENERAL SUPPORT GRANTS FOR COMMUNITY EDUCATIONAL TELEVISION STATIONS
  - Educational Broadcasting Corporation (06700593), 1967 October 17-1972 April 16 (Reel 5483)
    PAYMENT OF A DEBT TO THE NATIONAL EDUCATIONAL TELEVISION AND RADIO CENTER
    $1,825,000.00;$1,825,000.00
    Catalano, Richard M.
  - Educational Broadcasting Corporation (06800097), 1967 December 28-1968 March 27 (Reel 1369)
    SPECIAL DAYTIME BROADCASTS OF SELECTED SESSIONS OF THE ANNUAL MEETING OF THE AMER. ASSO. FOR THE ADVANCEMENT OF SCIENCE
  - Educational Broadcasting Corporation (06800233), 1968 April 03-1978 April 02 (Reel 5651)
  - Educational Broadcasting Corporation (06800683), 1968 July 12-1969 October 01 (Reel 1675)
    $631,000.00;$631,000.00
  - Educational Broadcasting Corporation (06900344), 1969 May 02-1970 May 01 (Reel 2002)
    SUPPORT FOR PUBLIC TELEVISION STATIONS AND NETWORKS FOR CULTURAL, PUBLIC AFFAIRS AND CHILDREN'S PROGRAM SERIES
    $666,100.00;$666,100.00
  - Educational Broadcasting Corporation (07000132), 1970 January 01-1971 December 31 (Reel 1412)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT OF THE COSTS OF PRODUCING 20 ONE-HOUR "SOUL!" PROGRAMS FOR NATIONAL DISTRIBUTION
    Davis, David M.;Sucherman, Stuart F.
  - Educational Broadcasting Corporation (07000404), 1970 June 26-1971 June 25 (Reel 5837)
    PARTIAL SUPP. FOR COSTS OF PRODUCING 20 ONE-HOUR SOUL! PROGRAMS FOR NATIONAL DISTRIBUTION BY THE PUBLIC BROADCASTING SERVICE
    Sucherman, Stuart F.
  - Educational Broadcasting Corporation (07100020), 1970 October 01-1972 October 31 (Reel 1743;3882)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT FOR THE NET OPERA PROJECT
    $620,000.00;$620,000.00
  - Educational Broadcasting Corporation (07100075), 1971 February 08-1972 February 07 (Reel 1712)
    GENERAL SUPPORT OF NATIONAL AND LOCAL PUBLIC TELEVISION PROGRAMMING
    $8,000,000.00;$8,000,000.00
  - Educational Broadcasting Corporation (07100094), 1971 January 01-1971 June 30 (Reel 4179)
    SUPPORT OF LOCAL TELEVISION PROGRAMMING & CERTAIN DEVELOPMENTAL COSTS OF A DAILY "NEWS" SHOW
    $1,200,000.00;$1,200,000.00
  - Educational Broadcasting Corporation (07100298), 1970 December 01-1972 November 30 (Reel 1227)
    SUPPORT FOR THE ACTIVITIES OF THE NATIONAL PROGRAMMING COUNCIL FOR PUBLIC TELEVISION
    $99,100.00;$99,100.00
    Streibert, Catherine
  - Educational Broadcasting Corporation (07100426), 1971 July 01-1972 June 30 (Reel 1073)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT FOR ONE NINETY MINUTE FILM ON POWER PRODUCTION PRODUCED BY NET
  - Educational Broadcasting Corporation (07200070), 1972 January 31-1973 January 30 (Reel 1346;5201)
    SUPPORT FOR THE PURCHASE OF CAPITAL EQUIPMENT
    $2,200,000.00;$2,200,000.00
  - Educational Broadcasting Corporation (07200180), 1972 July 01-1973 June 30 (Reel 1744)
    GENERAL SUPPORT OF NATIONAL PUBLIC TELEVISION PROGRAMMING
    $4,040,000.00;$4,040,000.00
  - Educational Broadcasting Corporation (07200317), 1972 July 01-1973 June 30 (Reel 1753;1754)
    SUPPORT OF LOCAL PROGRAMMING
  - Educational Broadcasting Corporation (07300164), 1973 February 05-1973 August 04 (Reel 1767)
    TO PROVIDE STATION COSTS IN CONNECTION WITH THE STATION INDEPENDENCE PROJECT
    $74,480.00;$21,053.00
  - Educational Broadcasting Corporation (07300521), 1973 June 15-1974 June 14 (Reel 1772)
    GENERAL SUPPORT OF NATIONAL PUBLIC TELEVISION PROGRAMMING PRODUCED FOR THE 1973-74 BROADCAST YEAR
    Streibert, Catherine;Sucherman, Stuart F.
  - Educational Broadcasting Corporation (07400225), 1973 July 01-1974 June 30 (Reel 1251)
    Davis, David M.;Streibert, Catherine
  - Educational Broadcasting Corporation (07400343), 1974 April 01-1978 June 30 (Reel 2430;2431)
    SUPPORT FOR PROGRAMMING AND FOR WORKING AND PROGRAMMING CAPITAL PRODUCTION CENTERS AND PBS
    $10,000,000.00;$10,000,000.00
    North America; Educational Broadcasting Corporation
  - Educational Broadcasting Corporation (07400584), 1974 July 01-1975 June 30 (Reel 1298)
    SUPPORT OF NATIONAL PROGRAMMING
    $2,424,000.00;$2,424,000.00
  - Educational Broadcasting Corporation (07600021), 1975 July 01-1977 June 30 (Reel 1417)
    SUPPORT FOR NATIONAL PROGRAMMING OF THE PUBLIC BROADCASTING SERVICE THROUGH JUNE 1976
    $1,827,689.00;$1,827,689.00
    United States; Educational Broadcasting Corporation
  - Educational Broadcasting Corporation (07600192), 1976 April 15-1976 October 14 (Reel 1227)
    SUPPORT FOR TWO PILOT PROGRAMS FOR A PROPOSED PUBLIC TELEVISION SERIES ENTITLED "THE SUPREME COURT"
  - Educational Broadcasting Corporation (07600195), 1976 April 21-1976 October 20 (Reel 1224)
    SUPPORT FOR PRODUCTION COSTS IN PROVIDING COVERAGE OF '76 PRESIDENTIAL FORUMS FOR THE PBS NETWORK
    $20,000.00;$19,808.00
  - Educational Broadcasting Corporation (07600256), 1976 April 30-1976 October 29 (Reel 1301)
    PORTIAL SUPPORT FOR PRODUCTION OF THE PILOT PROGRAM OF THE PUBLIC T.V. SERIES ENTITLED"US" FOR THE WORKING CLASS AUDIENCE
    National Affairs [NA];Office of Communications (pre 1979)
    Davis, David M.;Goldmann, Robert B.
  - Educational Broadcasting Corporation (07650181), 1976 (Reel 1602)
    TO STUDY FEASIBILITY OF CONVERTING CHANNEL 31 FACILITIES INTO AN EDUCATIONAL BROADCASTING SYSTEM IN COOPERATION WITH EDUCATIONAL
    $22,800.00;$22,800.00
    Spangeberg, Gail
  - Educational Broadcasting Corporation (07700600), 1977 October 01-1985 December 31 (Reel 6207)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT FOR THE FUND FOR INDEPENDENT DOCUMENTARIES FOR PUBLIC TELEVISION AT THE TELEVISION LABORATORY, WNET/13
    $1,450,000.00;$1,450,000.00
  - Educational Broadcasting Corporation (07800535), 1978 July 01-1980 June 30 (Reel 3686)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT OF THE FIRST TWO SEASONS OF "BILL MOYERS JOURNAL"
    $1,800,000.00;$1,800,000.00
  - Educational Broadcasting Corporation (07800923), 1978 October 01-1979 September 30 (Reel 2508)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT OF A THREE PART DOCUMENTARY, "THE OPIUM TRILOGY"
  - Educational Broadcasting Corporation (07850385), 1978 March 01-1979 February 28 (Reel 2403)
    SUPPORT FOR WORK ON PUBLICITY SERVICES FOR THE PRODUCTIONS AWARDEDFROM THE INDEPENDENT DOCUMENTARY FUND
    $10,850.00;$10,850.00
    Friendly, Fred W.;Zimmerman, Nancy K.
  - Educational Broadcasting Corporation (07900396), 1979 May 01-1980 December 31 (Reel 4692)
    TV DOCUMENTARY ON CHILDREN'S INCARCERATION AND THE YOUTHFUL OFFENDER SYSTEM
    $88,000.00;$88,000.00
  - Educational Broadcasting Corporation (08100173), 1981 January 01-1981 July 31 (Reel 3621)
    SUPPORT FOR THE PRODUCTION OF A DOCUMENTARY FILM ON THE SUBJECT OF THE SOUTH BRONX
    $43,235.00;$43,235.00
    McDonald, Bernard
  - Educational Broadcasting Corporation (08100239), 1981 January 26-1982 January 25 (Reel 3611)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT FOR VIDEO SERIES TO TEACH YOUNG ADOLESCENTS TO MAKE INFORMED JUDGEMENTS ABOUT TELEVISION VIEWING
  - Educational Broadcasting Corporation (08600997), 1986 September 01-1988 December 31 (Reel 6393)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT FOR FIVE ONE-HOUR PROGRAMS DESIGNED TO PROVIDE A FRAMEWORK FOR UNDERSTANDING THE SOVIET-AMERICAN CONFLICT
    Balaran, Paul
    Soviet Union; United States; Educational Broadcasting Corporation
  - Educational Broadcasting Corporation (08700284), 1986 July 01-1987 June 30 (Reel 5479)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT OF WNET/THIRTEEN'S METROLINE 1986-87 SERIES ON URBAN PROBLEMS AND CONCERNS
    New York (N.Y.); Educational Broadcasting Corporation
  - Educational Broadcasting Corporation (08800339), 1987 November 01-1988 October 31 (Reel 5769)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT OF WNET/THIRTEEN'S METROLINE 1987-88 SERIES ON URBAN PROBLEMS AND CONCERNS
    Gaberman, Barry D.
  - Educational Broadcasting Corporation (09000157), 1989 October 01-1993 November 30 (Reel 6400)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT FOR WNET'S THE DANCE PROJECT (008)
    Education & Culture Program [EC];US & International Affairs Programs - Office Of Vice President [USIAP/OVP]
    Mayleas, Ruth R.;Taylor, Andrea L.;Vincent, Christine J.
  - Educational Broadcasting Corporation (09201042), 1992 June 01-1993 November 30 (Reel 6393;6441)
    FILM PROJECT ON AFRICAN AMERICAN SOLDIERS AND THE LIBERATION OF JEWISH SURVIVORS OF CONCENTRATION CAMPS (008)
    US & International Affairs Programs - Office Of Vice President [USIAP/OVP];Rights And Social Justice Program [RSJ]
    Taylor, Andrea L.;Huntley, Lynn
  - Educational Broadcasting Corporation (09301465), 1993 June 01-1994 November 30 (Reel 6668)
    SUPPORT FOR A DOCUMENTARY FILM ON WELFARE (008)
    Urban Poverty Program [UP];Rural Poverty & Resources Program [RPR];US & International Affairs Programs - Office Of Vice President [USIAP/OVP]
    Campbell, Elizabeth C.;Kubisch, Anne C.;Taylor, Andrea L.
  - Educational Broadcasting Corporation (09600283), 1995 October 01-1997 January 31 (Reel 7413)
    SUPPORT FOR INFORMATION DISSEMINATION TO URBAN TEENS
    Mohamed, Inca A.
  - Educational Broadcasting Corporation (09600695), 1996 May 01-1997 April 30 (Reel 7948)
    SUPPORT FOR A TELEVISION SERIES ON THE FEDERALIST PAPERS UTILIZING THE "FRED FRIENDLY SEMINARS" FORMAT
    Governance And Public Policy Program [GPP];Media [MEDIA]
    Lipsky, Michael;Santos, John Phillip
  - Educational Broadcasting Corporation (09801689), 1998 September 01-2000 February 29 (Reel 8478)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT FOR THE PRODUCTION OF NEW YORK, A DOCUMENTARY SOCIAL HISTORY OF NEW YORK CITY
    Governance and Civil Society;Education, Sexuality, Religion;Media Arts and Culture;Human Development and Reproductive Health;Unit Reserve;PSJ - Office of the Vice President;Human Rights
    $607,000.00;$607,000.00
    Aguerrebere, Joseph;Floyd, Virginia Davis;Funabiki, Jon;Higashi, Taryn;Jenkins, Alan;Reis, Kyle
    United States; New York (N.Y.); Social history; Documentary television programs -- New York (State) -- New York (State); Educational Broadcasting Corporation
  - Educational Broadcasting Corporation (09900612), 1999 March 01-2000 February 29 (Reel 8249)
    FOR EDUCATIONAL OUTREACH & WEB-BASED DISSEMINATION ACTIVITIES FOR "NEW YORK," A PBS DOCUMENTARY SERIES ON HISTORY OF NEW YORK CITY
    Santos, John Phillip
    New York (State); Educational Broadcasting Corporation
  - Educational Broadcasting Corporation (10200627), 2002 March 01-2003 February 28 (Reel 8850)
    For already-aired and future programming which directly relates to the September 11 crisis and its repercussions
    New York (State); Mass media; World Trade Center September 11 Terrorist Attacks, 2001; Educational Broadcasting Corporation
  - Educational Broadcasting Corporation (10300536), 2003 February 01-2005 February 28 (Reel 9171)
    To develop, produce and distribute WNET's international news documentary series Wide Angle and a specially edited set of videos for classroom use
    Media Arts and Culture;Education, Sexuality, Religion